Live fearlessly. Love endlessly.
The Sky Is Everywhere is a drama, romance, music
film directed by Josephine Decker.
Lennie is a teen musical prodigy grieving the death of her sister when she finds herself
caught between a new guy at school and her sister's devastated boyfriend.
Through her vivid imagination and conflicted heart,
Lennie navigates first love and first loss.
Lennie, played by Grace Kaufman.
Joe Fontaine, played by Jacques Colimon.
Fiona, played by Cherry Jones.
Big, played by Jason Segel.
Toby Shaw, played by Pico Alexander.
Sarah, played by Ji-young Yoo.
The Sky Is Everywhere is a 2022 American coming-of-age romantic drama film directed by Josephine
Decker and written by Jandy Nelson, based on the 2010 novel of the same name.
The film stars Grace Kaufman, Pico Alexander, Jacques
Colimon, Cherry Jones, and Jason Segel.
The Sky Is Everywhere was released on February 11, 2022, by A24 and Apple TV+.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, loss of
loved one, grief, teenage girl, death of sister.
The tone is emotional.